<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lab Riset Sosial</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lab Riset Sosial</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Covid-19 di Daerah Istimewa Yogyakarta</title>
      <link>/2021/06/01/covid-19-di-daerah-istimewa-yogyakarta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/06/01/covid-19-di-daerah-istimewa-yogyakarta/</guid>
      <description>Latar BelakangProyek ini merupakan proyek yang terdapat pada DQLAB, dimana merupakan hasil eksplorasi sederhana terhadap data Covid-19 di Indonesia, Data yang digunakan diambil langsung dari API (Application Programming Interface) yang tersedia di covid19.go.id. Sehingga dalam proyek ini akan mempelajari terkait pengambilan data dari API hingga melakukan visualisasi data.
Mengakses API covid.go.id
Rekapitulasi data COVID-19 Indonesia tersedia dalam API publik yang beralamat di ___https://data.covid19.go.id/public/api/update.json___. Salah satu cara untuk mengakses API adalah dengan menggunakan fungsi GET() dari paket httr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find Suitable Systems and Policy to Enhance Indonesia Education Quality Through Its PISA Result: Compare with Finland Education System</title>
      <link>/2021/04/18/find-suitable-systems-and-policy-to-enhance-indonesia-education-quality-through-its-pisa-result-compare-with-finland-education-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2021/04/18/find-suitable-systems-and-policy-to-enhance-indonesia-education-quality-through-its-pisa-result-compare-with-finland-education-system/</guid>
      <description>Tawang K. Utami Universitas Negeri Yogyakarta
Abstract
The aim of this paper is to examine how public and international pressures affect the education policy in Indonesia. The method used in collecting data was by utilizing secondary data and compiling news from international finding. The news compilation was analyzed using discourse analysis to depict the public pressure to change the curriculum in Indonesia.
Introduction
Education is a program that can be linked with teaching and learning certain disciplines in order to understand the accumulated science in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a &amp;ldquo;hello world&amp;rdquo; example website for the blogdown package. The theme was forked from @jrutheiser/hugo-lithium-theme and modified by Yihui Xie.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
